http://www.mvpvisuals.com/pages/privacy-policy

Drapes
Non Printed Flame Retardant - Black Out Performance Velour Drapes
Hours: M-F, 8am-6pm EST
Resources.
Why Choose MVP?
Drapes
Non Printed Flame Retardant - Black Out Performance Velour Drapes
0
No products in the cart.
Privacy Policy
Home
Privacy Policy
PRIVACY STATEMENT
WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?
When you purchase something from our store, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address.
When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system. Email marketing (if applicable): With your permission, we may send you emails about our products and other updates.
HOW DO YOU GET MY CONSENT? When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.
If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.
HOW DO I WITHDRAW MY CONSENT? If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdrawing your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at any time, by contacting us at hello@mvpvisuals.com or mailing us at:
MVP Visuals27 Quality Avenue, Somers, CT 06071
DISCLOSURE
We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.
SHOPIFY
Our store is hosted on Shopify Inc. They provide us with the online e-commerce platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you.  Your data is stored through Shopify’s data storage, databases and the general Shopify application. They store your data on a secure server behind a firewall.
Payment: If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then Shopify stores your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted. All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover.  PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card.
By using our website, you (the visitor) agree to allow third parties to process your IP address, in order to determine your location for the purpose of currency conversion. You also agree to have that currency stored in a session cookie in your browser (a temporary cookie which gets automatically removed when you close your browser). We do this in order for the selected currency to remain selected and consistent when browsing our website so that the process can convert to your (the visitor) local currency.
Company
About UsBlogFAQ Videos
Quick Quote
Resources
ArtworkTemplatesSample RequestDistributorsSuccess StoriesWarranty
Industries
AgenciesEntertainmentFood & BeverageNon-ProfitsRun & Walk EventsSports Teams
© MVP Visuals 2019.
